<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on $ cd /home/</title>
    <link>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on $ cd /home/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mikedido.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus tracker</title>
      <link>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/coronavirus-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/coronavirus-tracker/</guid>
      <description>About During the first lockdown hearing about COVID-19 all day long prompted me to develop a small app to visualize the evolution of the pandemic around the world. An application to analyze data on the coronavirus / COVID-19 virus by giving the number of deaths, confirmed, active person recovered worldwide. The app provides detailed information in each country. Charts and histograms are available to assess the number of deaths, confirmed active and recovering by country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ilot</title>
      <link>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/ilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/ilot/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents  Introduction Architecture  2.1. The corpus 2.2. Population step  2.2.1 Annotation 2.2.2 Population   2.3 Enrichment step  2.3.1 With general data 2.3.2 With specific data   2.4 Exploitation step   Partenaires Publications Links  Introduction The ILOT (Innovative Learning Object for Teaching) project is a collaborative project that combines Gutenberg technologies, LeLivreScolaire, Alcatel Lucent et Telecom ParisTech to provide a resource repository pedagogical allowing the collaborative development of such resources, their annotation and their use in different modes of consultation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScaleSem</title>
      <link>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/scalesem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikedido.github.io/projects/scalesem/</guid>
      <description>About The increasing development of networks and especially the Internet has greatly expanded the gap between heterogeneous information systems. In a review of studies of interoperability of heterogeneous information systems, we find that all the work in this area tends to be in solving the problems of semantic heterogeneity. The W3C (World Wide Web Consortium) standards proposed to represent the semantic ontology. Ontology is becoming an indispensable support for interoperability of information systems, and in particular the semantics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
